[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Here,
have a bite of the bun.
[Half a month ago]
Never thought
I'd take in a sidekick here.
He's called Lyu Ruhui.
He's really something.
He masters some mystical tricks.
The guy's quite tall
and energetic,
with thick eyebrows
and big eyes.
Blessing generations to come!
He actually pulled off the trick of Three Immortals Eating Noodles.
I told him to follow me,
and I'd have his back.
Were it not for this young man,
I would've died on the Corpse Driving journey.
I'm a human!
Who would've thought those bastards were smuggling opium?
Opium paste?
Also,
he said he was going to the Qian family's place.
He said his name isn't Lyu Ruhui.
My real name isn't Lyu Ruhui.
My name is Shangguan Chengming.
[A Prophet]
[Episode 7]
[Qianshan Station]
[Seven days ago]
It's indeed not enough for me.
Spare me, sir!
We're all
in the same business.
Second Master,
someone is here to see you.
You didn't expect this, did you?
I'm still alive.
Who are you?
You threw me into the river,
and you've already forgotten it?
This guy is a fraud!
He used my name
to sneak into Longxuya
and got Chief Du killed!
You have nothing to back that up.
Why should we believe you?
When the incident happened at Longxuya,
I saw him
with Feng Siyuan.
This guy
used Feng Siyuan
to wipe out Longxuya.
He's now targeting your Qian family!
Is what he said true?
What are you doing?
Second Brother!
Was he telling the truth?
Yes,
I work for Commander Feng.
Blind Du is a mere opium smuggler.
The real source
is the buyer pulling the strings—
Mingcao Hall,
the Qian family.
What does the Qian family have to do with this?
On the surface, the Qian family runs a herbal medicine business.
But behind the scenes,
they make the drugs collected from Blind Du
into an ointment called Bashen Powder,
raking in money
and harming the people.
Your empty words
are hardly convincing.
All the Qian family's shady deeds
are recorded in a secret ledger.
If we can bring it to light,
Commander Feng,
you will be upholding justice for all.
I've always engraved Mr. Sun's saying in my heart—
the world belongs to the public.
If you can raid the Qian family,
you'll rid the people
of the threat of drugs for the public good.
You'll confiscate
the illicit possessions and keep the region safe, also for the public good.
This is
a good deal for the public good.
I also keep
Mr. Sun's saying in my heart—
the world belongs to the public.
"The world belongs to the public." Nice.
But
I need to borrow something from you
before I visit the Qian family this time.
Go ahead.
Why should I trust you?
You can check the license plate out there
and see if it's from the division headquarters.
What if it's a stolen one?
And what if I really am Commander Feng's man?
Can you bear the consequences
of offending the Commander, Second Master?
Third Madam.
A group of soldiers is at the door.
The leader says they're here to deliver a gift.
The grand gift has arrived.
Let him in.
Yes, Ma'am.
Sir,
here is what you asked for.
Commander Feng ordered me
to hand it to you personally.
Put it on the table.
Yes, Sir.
Second Master, won't you open it
to see if you like
the gift?
Who exactly are you?
Aren't you good at fortune-telling, Second Master?
You businessmen believe
that investments must yield returns.
We in the military have a rule too.
Once a gun is drawn, it must be fired.
Second Master,
take aim.
Mr. Chengming,
please calm down.
I can't.
He is right.
I did wipe out the entire Longxuya Branch for Commander Feng.
Do you know why?
Because those frauds
used our soldiers' bodies to smuggle opium.
They were soldiers,
brothers to Commander Feng and me.
Not your tools for making money.
What exactly is going on?
I...
I don't know.
Second Master.
If someone desecrated your brothers' bodies,
would you just let it go?
Mr. Chengming,
Mr. Chengming, please calm down.
What soldiers?
We really have no idea.
If Blind Du
really did such a heartless thing,
then he deserved to die.
Such a man who deserved to die
was supposed to be executed in public.
But he died the night before the execution.
Don't you think he got off easy?
Then
who did it?
The Tianxiang Sect.
You and Blind Du
smuggled drugs behind the Sect Master's back.
Blind Du's death
was the Sect Master making an example of him.
But if your Bashen Powder
is escorted by our army,
you won't have to worry
about the Tianxiang Sect seeking revenge.
After all, in these chaotic times,
what is safer than having the army's backing?
Then
how much does
Commander Feng want?
Commander Feng said
he only wants 30 percent of the profit.
What if I refuse?
Second Master, why do you
think your whole family is still
living in peace?
To show his sincerity,
Commander Feng has told the Sect Master
not to touch your family.
Commander Feng also said
that harmony brings wealth.
Second Master, don't listen to him.
He sent a severed head.
What harmony and wealth is he talking about?
Amitabha.
You...
Mr. Chengming.
If we can
cooperate with Commander Feng this time,
it will be a great blessing for the Qian family.
But this is a matter of great importance.
Please allow my brother and me to discuss it further.
As for the business,
I can afford to wait.
I'm just afraid
Commander Feng cannot.
I apologize
for the offense today.
Please stay at our residence for a few days.
My second brother and sister-in-law are getting married.
If you don't mind,
please join us for the wedding.
It can also be considered a good omen
for our future cooperation.
So, Second Master, your wedding is approaching.
Then I thank you
in advance for the wedding drink.
Huaiyi.
What happened?
Shuyi.
It's a mess in here.
Let me have the servants clean it up.
Listen to me.
Don't be afraid of whatever you see later.
I'm here.
What exactly happened?
How could this happen?
This is so unlucky
right before the wedding.
Bear with it.
There are outsiders here.
Let me introduce her.
This is
the woman I'm about to marry,
Jiang Shuyi.
Chengming,
I'm
a reckless man.
Don't take what just happened
to heart.
Just as you said,
harmony
brings wealth.
Do you know
Lyu Ruhui is from the Tianxiang Sect?
How can I explain to the Tianxiang Sect if you kill him?
The Tianxiang Sect has already killed Blind Du.
We
will be next.
Our business of the Bashen Powder
has already broken the Sect Master's rules.
Wouldn't it be a good thing
to have Commander Feng as our backer?
Besides, they only want 30% of the profit.
Can't you figure out this deal, Second Brother?
Do you know what you're talking about?
Am I the one who can't figure it out now?
Feng has his eyes
on our Bashen Powder now.
So he eliminated Longxuya on the surface first.
Now he sent someone over
to hypocritically talk about cooperation with us.
He said he wants 30%.
30%
wouldn't even be enough for him.
The reason Feng hasn't touched our family yet
is that only we know how to make the Bashen Powder.
One day,
when we are squeezed dry by Feng,
our fate will be worse than Blind Du's.
Huaiyi!
You are destined to face a disaster
this year.
I practice every day
just to ward off disasters for you.
Huaiyi.
I'm taking the blame for this killing
for you today.
Sister,
I won't say anything about you messing with these things
usually,
but now
you're believing in the Buddha at home
and worshipping masters outside.
Let me tell you,
they are all clay idols.
Second Madam Qian.
You weren't even going to invite me to your wedding?
Only relatives and friends
will come to the wedding.
I've only just met you, Mr. Chengming.
Why would I have invited you?
Whether you invite me or not,
I'm already here.
I just wonder whether this marriage
is real or not.
What if it's real,
and what if it's fake?
If it's real,
I naturally have to prepare a big gift.
If it's fake...
Maybe I can help.
Stay out of my business.
Keep quiet.
Second Madam Qian.
I'm here.
Is the road smooth?
Everything is normal.
The Sect Master said
to close the net early.
We must get the money as soon as possible.
I'll act immediately when I find a chance.
Then rest early.
Isn't the Qian family with the Tianxiang Sect?
Would your own people attack your own?
Cooperating with Feng Siyuan
is like asking a tiger for its hide.
I advise you not to play with fire.
Shouldn't you give me an explanation
for what happened back then?
You wouldn't believe whatever I say anyway.
Do it.
Mr. Chengming.
Want to die?
It's not that simple.
Your life alone
can't make up for the lives of my whole family.
I know.
You're coming for the entire Tianxiang Sect.
He's just a fraud.
He sneaked into Longxuya using my name
and killed Chief Du.
Now he's coming for your Qian family.
Honey, was my snoring
keeping you awake?
Tomorrow,
go to Commander Feng's division headquarters.
Check Shangguan Chengming's identity.
Honey, rest assured.
Shangguan Chengming has nothing to do
with the Tianxiang Sect.
He came here
with Blind Du’s head.
Understood, Honey.
I'll send someone there first thing tomorrow morning.
Amitabha.
Third Madam,
you invited me to this salvation ritual today,
and I can see
you have
the compassion to deliver all beings from suffering.
You flatter me, Mr. Shangguan.
I wonder if you and the Second Master
have reached a decision regarding this partnership?
I am naturally willing
to cooperate with Commander Feng.
It's just that...
Third Madam.
Who exactly calls the shots in your family?
Buddhism or Taoism,
you have to pick one.
You don't seem like someone who is easily swayed.
If you think this deal is viable,
hand over the account book for the Bashen Powder.
Once Commander Feng reviews it,
we have
a deal.
The account book?
Since we are working together,
the accounts
naturally must be clear.
I follow the righteous decree
to pacify the wandering souls.
May all beings be sheltered
and all creations receive grace.
May each return to their true nature.
Let compassion spread
and bless the universe.
Bestow boundless mercy.
Obey my command at once!
Break!
Master.
Master, are you alright?
-Master. -It’s fine.
I had already sent away
Lyu Ruhui's vengeful spirit,
but an unknown
surge of evil aura
trapped his spirit
in the Qian family again.
Where would our family get an evil aura?
While fighting that evil aura,
I vaguely saw
it was formed by a book.
If I am not mistaken,
it should be
Yama's
Book of Life and Death.
The Book of Life and Death?
This...
How could our family have such a thing?
The records in that book
concern the lives and deaths of many.
But as to what exactly it is,
I must trouble you to think carefully,
Third Madam.
Master.
Then,
is there any other way
to appease this vengeful spirit?
Lyu Ruhui
is tightly bound by the evil aura of the Book of Life and Death.
He cannot leave.
To completely resolve this,
Third Madam,
you must find this
Book of Life and Death.
Help!
Stay away!
Honey.
It's me. It's me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
There's...
There's nothing.
What did you see?
Nothing.
Are you under too much stress lately?
It's okay.
Wenxin,
tell me,
could the Book of Life and Death
Master Chang mentioned
be the ledger
in Huaiyi's hands?
Why do you say that?
Didn't the Master say
every sum of money in that ledger
represents a human life?
Isn't that the Book of Life and Death?
But the Bashen Powder is all off the books.
Our ledger only records
our dealings
with the Tianxiang Sect.
Wouldn't it be a bad idea to hand it over to someone else?
Besides,
knowing your second brother,
he wouldn't give it to you anyway.
Whether he gives it to me or not, I have to try!
Otherwise...
Otherwise, our family may
never make it through this ordeal.
I'll figure something out.
It's okay.
Sir.
She gets scared easily.
I haven't even started yet.
Here.
It's hot.
Here, Chengming.
Try this.
I had someone make this duck soup just for you.
That's very thoughtful of you, Wenxin.
Don't mention it.
Have a taste.
Alright.
The broth is made with foxnuts and Job's tears.
It nourishes Yin, reduces internal heat, and replenishes your energy.
See how it tastes.
It tastes good.
Wenxin, you didn't come today
just to bring me a bowl of soup, right?
Chengming,
rest assured.
I will do whatever it takes
to get that ledger for you.
Not everyone
can see the situation
as clearly as you do.
If we can make this deal happen,
you'll
have earned the most credit.
My friend,
if I get this done,
I have a favor to ask.
Honey,
I've asked around.
Shangguan Chengming is indeed Commander Feng's adjutant.
The Master once told our family
that we'd eventually face a great ordeal.
He wrote this poem while giving me guidance.
Look at the last line.
This character is Commander Feng's surname, isn't it?
"Finally meeting a worthy man"—
doesn't that mean Commander Feng?
It has to be Commander Feng.
That makes sense.
Huaiyi,
before our wedding,
I asked a married woman blessed with good fortune to comb my hair.
She told me
to leave this comb here
for a few days as an offering
for good luck.
Master.
Madam.
I've brought it for you.
It...
It's broken.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just leave it to me.
The Red Phoenix Star shines over you both—
great joy is on its way.
Madam,
your face is glowing like a peach blossom;
you will bring your husband good fortune and prosperity to the family.
You are destined
to turn misfortune into good fortune.
Huaiyi, look.
Didn't it just break?
Turn misfortune into good fortune.
What does that mean?
You came for money,
and you will leave for money.
Benefactor,
is your surname Qian—money?
Then, Master,
tell me,
what is my surname?
Half full, half empty.
The water god Gonggong does not cause a flood.
Your
surname is Jiang—river.
Then what did you mean
by the misfortune
you just mentioned?
Once you enter the military, thousands will die.
You hold snow with wet hands and never make it home.
Your current situation
is like being trapped
among thousands upon thousands of troops.
Then, Master,
is there anything I can do
to avert it?
I'm afraid
you've recently meddled in a karmic matter you shouldn't have.
You'd better
make plans early.
That's
all I can say.
Thank you, Master.
It's a good thing we came here today.
We really need to watch our backs
from now on.
I think
what he said makes some sense.
We did offend Commander Feng recently.
I just can't shake the feeling
that something's not right.
Huaiyi,
don't you think
we'd be better off keeping
the money ourselves?
What if
we have children someday?
We wouldn't want them to starve, would we?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of
both you
and our kids.
Stop worrying.
Chengming,
if I get this done,
I have a favor to ask.
Please speak your mind.
I'd like
to serve under you, if you could find me a position...
Alright.
You have my word.
Thank you.
If this deal
really is thanks to you,
from now on,
you won't ever have to
live by other people's whims again.
What are you looking for?
Huai...
Huaiyi.
What are you looking for?
Tell me,
and I'll help you find it.
Huaiyi,
what's all this
commotion about?
Chengming,
please don't take offense.
Since we'll be doing business together from now on,
I asked you to join us today and see for yourself
and learn about
the rules our Qian family
has passed down through the generations.
Huaiyi.
Honey.
I asked everyone here today
because
there is a thief
in the Qian family.
I am not a thief.
If you are not a thief,
what were you doing in my study?
I...
Were you trying to steal money?
No,
absolutely not.
If it was not money, then what?
Someone.
Bring out the family punishment.
Huaiyi,
we haven't gotten to the bottom of this yet.
Don't do anything rash.
Shuyi,
sit down.
A country has its laws,
and a family has its rules.
No matter who he is,
he must
conduct himself.
Talk.
What were you doing in my study?
Wenxin,
I'll give you one last chance.
Talk.
What exactly were you trying to steal
from my study?
Chengming is right.
We have no choice but to cooperate with Commander Feng now.
It's only natural that he wants to see the ledger.
Why are you still hesitating?
It seems
someone is backing you up.
You've even got the nerve to talk to me like this.
Huaijin.
So this is the dog you've been raising.
Careful, one day
this ungrateful beast
will bite you back.
Honey.
How could he be so ruthless?
Wenxin,
everyone was there.
I had no choice
but to hit you.
Come on.
Give it to me.
I brought our ancestral wound medicine.
Let me put some on.
Does it hurt?
Hang in there.
Miss Shuyi,
I've brought your bird's nest porridge.
Come in.
Enjoy.
After Zhou Wenxin's scene,
it seems Second Master has come around
to depositing the money.
The Sect Master wants to know
when you're going to make your move.
Today.
Everything's ready?
Why are you sweating so much?
Huaiyi,
are you sure you want to put all this money
in my name
instead of leaving it with Huaijin?
Huaijin and Zhou Wenxin are clearly in on it together.
I think they
have fallen for Shangguan Chengming's scheme.
They're not
the ones who get to call the shots in this family.
Actually, Huaijin
must have her own reasons.
Let's
give her the ledger.
That should make her feel better.
We'd already had something unpleasant happen that day.
If you upset everyone again,
how are we supposed to get married?
I don't want to
marry into your Qian family with everyone at odds.
Well, aren't you considerate?
Honey. You're truly understanding
and generous.
It's just that
my eldest brother
has always kept the ledger.
Speaking of which,
I'm also the future daughter-in-law of your Qian family.
Should I go
and visit your eldest brother?
No need.
My eldest brother is a bit eccentric
and rarely sees anyone.
You will naturally meet him
on our wedding day.
Hello, Miss.
Can I deposit this amount here
and withdraw it
in Nanyang?
As long as it's a Meifeng Bank branch,
you can withdraw it anywhere.
Sir,
that's too large an amount
for me to authorize.
I'll need to call our bank manager.
Can you call them now?
I'm in a hurry.
All right.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
This way, please.
Watch where you're going!
Are you blind?
That's enough, Huaiyi.
He didn't do it on purpose.
Don't be mad.
I'm sorry, sir.
Stupid.
Hello.
How can I help you?
I want to deposit some money.
Just a moment.
Once I've counted the money,
I'll give you the deposit certificate.
[Women's bathroom]
Okay, Manager.
I'm sorry, sir.
Our manager said the interest rate you're asking for is a bit high.
All right.
How about this?
I can settle for a lower interest rate,
as long as I can make a fixed-term deposit and withdraw it at maturity.
Could you please
talk to the manager again?
Okay.
Please have a seat.
Can you hurry up?
Sorry, Mr. Qian.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your deposit certificate.
You can withdraw it at any branch nationwide.
Just sign here.
Please keep this safe.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Let's go get that bag first.
You also like that bracelet, right?
No need, Huaiyi.
Huaiyi, Shuyi.
What a coincidence.
What brings you to the bank in person?
Come on.
Stop beating around the bush.
You're here to deposit money, aren't you, Huaiyi?
Huaijin,
whatever it is,
let's talk about it at home.
Second Master,
let me ask you something on Commander Feng's behalf.
Are you planning to transfer the money and run?
You say one thing to our faces and do another behind our backs.
Do you take me for a fool,
or do you think Commander Feng is someone you can push around?
I think
this is our family matter.
I can't interfere with your family matter.
But if you choose to learn the hard way,
when the Tiansang Sect comes knocking,
I hope
you'll still be this tough then.
Huaiyi,
Let's have a look
at the deposit certificate.
You deposited all the money in her name?
Huaijin,
you misunderstood.
Although the money is in my name,
Huaiyi was going to give you
this deposit certificate when he got home.
Without this deposit certificate,
no one can withdraw the money.
Since you trust me,
I'll hold on
to the deposit certificate for now.
This one.
Try them all.
All of them?
All of them.
This way, please.
Take your time.
Mr. Qian, let's take your measurements.
Let's measure your arm span first.
Coming.
Are you out of your mind?
[In the next episode]
Do you know
where the Qian family's
eldest master lives?
Who are you?
Who brought you here?
I'm here to buy some medicine.
You're here to buy medicine?
Please go upstairs.
Why didn't you light the lamp?
There's something wrong with this candle.
Wake up, bro.
Eldest Master.
Second Master and Second Madam
asked me to bring you some wedding candy.